[{"answer": "... it's interesting that you asked that.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "... question go ask?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, you've got a DUI allegation, you're talking about a breath reading that's under the legal limit which is 0.02.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "I do find what's happened down there quite fascinating because - with serious question I think should be asked now of the police and their behavior over this shouldn't it?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, if Justin Bieber is sort of a criminal light right now.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Is there a serious risk here of Bieber being deported?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I don't have anything to compare it to but he called 911 and the operator was very helpful just to kind of walk him through how -- I mean that they sure they -- just what exactly to do.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "And how did it all go?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "It was sheer blessing that everything went well, the girl was healthy and doing great.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Did you feel like it was unproblematic in the end despite the terrible situation?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, in my case, I mean I don't know Atlanta and the jurisdiction there.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Who is ultimately responsible?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, let's see, you have mentioned ...", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Well, and also I found -- what do I found with gun control?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "No he can't.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Can he?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "... half of it will get challenged in the courts, half of it will get all returned as being executive overreach.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "... do the things he's saying?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Ronald Reagan and Bill Clinton did.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Can any President in his position right now really achieve a great deal more in the rest of his second term?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "He can do more -- he can do more enforcement on the justice department.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "But what can he do about gun control saying without Congress?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "But I have to give away somethings that my constituents my not like.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Well, it's to do deal, right?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "It's the art of doing a political deal, isn't it?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Not prioritizing anything.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "But he is not prioritizing gun control, is he?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I know Michael, really (ph).", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Does New York politics meets New York media?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I don't think I've ever threatened.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Have you ever threaten to throw a reporter over balcony?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Well, I hope I ever did.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "I'm not -- I couldn't you imagine you possibly doing that Rudy?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "And it was a moment of real unity I felt last night, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I think Denver.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Who's going to win the Super Bowl?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "When I turn.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "...I guess of an innocence about it?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I think we became disconnected about 12 years ago and then when we lost him, Mau, Robin and I gravitated back towards each other a little bit and it's always been twins and the older brother.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Is that inevitable when two of your brothers are twins?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "It's, I guess, its' the difference between being a group and being brothers in a group or being sisters in a group, you know.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Is it the precious outside forces of fame and so on?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Because it's really about lost love in all young people.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Why that one?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Well, we met on the set of Top of the Pops when \"Massachusetts\" was number one and then we had a cup of tea in the canteen of the BBC and then we had a couple in -- and (inaudible) and time stood still.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Why did you marry her?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Because I think we've just always been in love.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "And how do you manage that because -- and so, this is so listed with broken marriages, how have you managed to sustain such a lasting love do you think?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Well, I think we've both loved.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "You've never looked to anyone else since she's always in love with you?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Because I hate looking at myself with different ages.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Hard to watch, why?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "It's OK.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "And how's the -- how's your voice on that, I mean, how is it compared to what it used to be?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Did people expect you to talk about that?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Did you and the Beatles hang out much or not?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Your brother Andy?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Is that part of the progress?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yeah, being around the microphone together.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "What would be your favorite memory or perhaps the big times with your brothers, not the early days (ph)?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "A song writing, beyond anything else and harmonies, you know, there was no great approach.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "What you would like the Bee Gees to stand forward to be remembered for, what do you think?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I was the Dolly role.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "So, you sang it?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I was not in costume.", "docId": "140129pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "But you're wearing costume?", "qSentId": 702}]